skenzo.com 2017-06-06

# Skenzo - Domain Parking Company | Exclusive Traffic Monetization Programs

## Privacy Policy

This Privacy Policy forms part of your legal agreement with us for use of Skenzo.com (Website.) and availing any of our products and services. We collect no personally identifiable information about you when you visit the Website unless you choose to provide that information to us or as specifically outlined in this Policy. Please read our Privacy Policy carefully to be sure you understand how we collect and use information and under what circumstances we share information about you. Skenzo is committed to protecting the privacy of its clients and online consumers. 

### We can modify this Privacy Policy

We reserve the right, in our sole discretion, to modify, add or delete provisions of this Privacy Policy at any time and from time to time. Your use of our Website after the effective date of any such modification, means you accept and agree to be bound by the Privacy Policy, as modified. We urge you to come back to this web page and review this Privacy Policy regularly so that you remain aware of the terms and conditions that apply to you. 

### Collecting personal information

"Personal Information" means any information obtained through your use of our Website which might reasonably be used to specifically identify you and may include your name, title, company, address, email and phone number, among other things.

We may collect and store any Personal Information you enter on our Website or provide to us in some other manner. This includes identifying information (such as your name, address, e-mail address, and telephone number), and any other personal information you choose to provide while using our Website or our services. 

### Collecting Anonymous. non-personal Information

We may collect non-personally identifiable information regarding the user's behavior and usage patterns on advertisements and sites operated by our clients to better customize the type of advertisements users see on various sites. 

Third Party List Information. We may also obtain both personal and non-personal information about you from third party data gathering sources. We may match this third-party collected information with the personally identifying information that you provide to us. 

Cookies, Web Beacons, and Other Information Collection Technology. We use various technologies to collect information from your computer and about your activities. For example, we collect and store non-personally identifying information through log files, cookies, clear gifs ("web beacons"), and third parties to create a profile of our users that details the users' viewing preferences. All such web beacons are used as part of the ad serving process and also help us collect information about a user's online interactions. 

  * 1.

Log Files. Technical information from your browser is automatically collected when you visit our Website. This information includes your IP address, your browser type, operating system, access times, the content of any undeleted cookies that your browser previously accepted from us (see "Cookies" below), and the referring website address. 

  * 2.

Cookies. A cookie is a piece of data stored on a user's computer that tracks non-personal information about the user. When using our Website, we may assign your computer one or more cookies which enable us to improve the quality of our service and to personalize your experience. Cookies allow us to automatically collect information about your activity on our Website, such as the web pages you visit, the links or advertisements you click, or the other actions you conduct while using our Website. The cookies do not store any personally identifiable information about you. Most browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to disable cookies. If you choose to disable cookies, you will still be able to access our Website, but you may not be able to use all of the interactive features we offer. 

  * 3.

Web Beacons. We, or our advertisers or partners, may use standard Internet technology such as web beacons (or "clear gifs"), tracking pixels, and other similar technologies, to gather aggregate, non-personally identifiable information about your use of our Website. 

  * 4.

Information collected by third-parties. We and our business partners, such as advertisers, may use tracking technologies, such as cookies, to collect information about users who view or interact with these advertisements and connect to other websites. This information allows us and our business partners to deliver targeted advertisements and gauge their effectiveness. Please note that we do not have access to or control over third parties' cookies used on our Website, and this policy does not govern the use of cookies by these third parties. 

  * 5.

Our technology collects and stores aggregated ad delivery reporting data. This data is used to provide our clients with campaign reporting and used for billing purposes. 

### Use of your information

Please note that we may use individual information for any legally permissible purpose in our sole discretion. Our ad serving technology does not collect any personally identifiable information about you during the ad delivery process. Accordingly, we are unable to provide access or the ability to change information stored by our technology. 

Service providers: We shall not share your personal information with third party service providers except as needed to perform their functions. 

Third parties for business reasons: In connection with a substantial corporate transaction, such as the sale of our business, a divestiture, merger, consolidation, or asset sale, or in the unlikely event of bankruptcy. If a change in ownership occurs that will result in your personal information being used in a manner different from that stated in the then-existing privacy policy, notification will be provided consistent with the terms of this Privacy Policy. 

Third parties for legal process: In response to a subpoena or similar investigative demand, a court order, or a request for cooperation from any law enforcement or other government agency; to establish or exercise our legal rights; to defend against legal claims; or as otherwise required by law. In such cases, we may raise or waive any legal objection or right available to us in our sole discretion. In addition, we may disclose your information when we believe it is appropriate in connection with efforts to investigate, prevent, or take other action regarding illegal activity, suspected fraud or other wrongdoing; to protect and defend the rights, property or safety of our company, our users, our employees, or others; to comply with applicable law or cooperate with law enforcement; or to enforce the terms of service of our Website or other agreements or policies. 

Aggregated and Non-Personal Information: We may rent, sell, or share aggregated demographic information not specifically identifiable to you, and other non-personal information we collect, with any third parties for any reason, including to develop and deliver targeted advertising, and to conduct general business analysis. The user information that we collect to create segments and profile information for our service is shared with our contracted customers and not with any other outside party. We may combine non-personal information we collect with additional non-personal information collected from other sources. Please note that our Privacy Policy does not cover any third party's use or handling of your information once it is shared. 

Links: Our Website contains links to other websites, including through advertisements. We are not responsible for the privacy practices of third party linked websites, even if our Website frames the linked third party website. We encourage you to be aware of when you leave our Website and to review the privacy statements of each and every website that you visit that collects personally identifiable information. This Privacy Policy applies solely to information we collect. Please note that we may present links in a format that enables us to understand whether they have been followed for aggregating informational purposes.

### Security

As you may appreciate, the Internet is a public network of networks and we cannot guarantee that communications between you and the Website or others, through or from our Website, will be free from unauthorized access or interference by third parties such as hackers. By using our Website, you are agreeing to assume this risk and any and all responsibility and liability that may arise. That said, the security of your Personal Information is important to us and when possible we attempt to provide secure transmissions by using encryption software. We have also put in place reasonable physical, electronic and operational procedures to safeguard information and we limit access to your Personal Information to only those employees who need access in order to perform their duties. 

### Contact Us

For questions or concerns relating to privacy, we can be contacted at: [privacy@skenzo.com](mailto:privacy@skenzo.com)
